<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Casper]]></title><description><![CDATA[A port of the casper blog built for gatsby]]></description><link>https://gatsby-casper.netlify.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 16:08:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Welcome to Ghost]]></title><description><![CDATA[A few things you should know upfront: Ghost is designed for ambitious, professional publishers who want to actively build a business around…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-casper.netlify.com/welcome/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-casper.netlify.com/welcome/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 23:46:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A few things you should know upfront&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghost is designed for ambitious, professional publishers who want to actively build a business around their content. That’s who it works best for.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The entire platform can be modified and customised to suit your needs. It’s very powerful, but does require some knowledge of code. Ghost is not necessarily a good platform for beginners or people who just want a simple personal blog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For the best experience we recommend downloading the Ghost Desktop App for your computer, which is the best way to access your Ghost site on a desktop device.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost is made by an independent non-profit organisation called the Ghost Foundation. We are 100% self funded by revenue from our Ghost(Pro) service, and every penny we make is re-invested into funding further development of free, open source technology for modern publishing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The version of Ghost you are looking at right now would not have been made possible without generous contributions from the open source community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Next up, the editor&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main thing you’ll want to read about next is probably: the Ghost editor. This is where the good stuff happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the way, once you’re done reading, you can simply delete the default &lt;strong&gt;Ghost&lt;/strong&gt; user from your team to remove all of these introductory posts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>